United States. You know, I was one of
these people that was very much even
though I'm a Pan-Africanist and even
though I'm from Grenada, I was very much
thinking of things in a bifurcated Well,
bifur is not the right word, but in a
truncated way, you know, looking at
things as if
they are not all interconnected. And
when you do that, you limit your ability
to actually
uh affect change. And so, it was
Palestine that made it imperative I mean
that it made it that made it, sorry.
That made it really, really clear for me
the bigger
the bigger work
that's at play
to keep people
to keep people in in in
entrenched
in
toxicity
in crime and harm
in chaos.
Huh?
What? Hm?
Hm?
I think Jordi just pressed the I love
you button.
Hm?
He's thinking.
I love you.
I don't believe anything Trump says.
I love you, Jordyn.
All done.
No, I'm not all done. Okay.
The loc maintenance has been going well.
You know, I'm learning.
I like that I don't have to like
wait.
You know, I like that I can just handle
business.
I like that a shady chick's hands are
not in my hair.
That was crazy how she flipped out on
me. Man, listen.
I beg you to save and clip
saying I love you and then I don't
believe anything Trump says then I love
you.
Why?
Do you think we will see in our
lifetimes their hold on humanity's
consciousness? I will.
I can't speak for anybody else, but I
will.
>> So,
don't believe the bots.
Don't believe the bots.
The bots will lie to you every time.
If you all haven't Have any of y'all
heard my album?
Miss Abby.
Oh, wow. Lemonade baked. That's Erica.
Thank you.
That's what's up, defined by love. Take
a listen. Take a listen.
I'm very proud of my album.
You'll be able to listen on Apple Music
probably this week.
But, you can support by paying
any amount that you desire by going to
amandadeevamusic.com.
>> I'll pin this.
Got to be a better way.
And we've got to make it.
There's got to be a better way.
So like, okay, if you see
you know the post that I posted about
Obama,
the song that's playing is my song,
Better Way.
I don't get paid for streaming at all.
I mean, you do, but it's like
a pittance.
Sci-Op is your fave, Neon? That's what's
up. I love hearing people's faves
because it's so fascinating to me which
songs resonate with people and, you
know, and why.
Actually, oh
I think I'm supposed to do an interview
right now.
>> Oh, no. Okay.
Tomorrow night
Tay
Black Girl News could have made the
album. Tomorrow night, I'll be
performing at Producer Sundays.
Uh I mean, sorry, Producer Mondays. My
boy Ray Angry, brilliant producer,
pianist, composer. He does a night every
Monday here in New York City and um I
will be performing at Producer Mondays.
So, if you're a late night folks,
um if you're a late night person, then
make sure you check it out. Stardust
Remix is your fav, Rica?
Every time someone says Stardust Remix
is their fav, I'm like I lose my mind.
Miss Debbie said Better Way is her
favorite. Yes. I don't really come to
ATL too often. Something about the vibe
in ATL has really changed.
You know, it's it's like
it used to be really really a dope
energy there, but these days
I feel like it's not the same level.
Someone said, "I want to be independent
media.
How do I get started?"
You start.
Hello, Walter Beasley. Thank you for
supporting my music.
You start making
you start
doing the research.
G said, "Yeah, I don't like it in
Atlanta, either."
So, the two links that you're looking at
are the link to my new album
Truth Translator.
Um and the link to
uh my sale
which is going on right now.
It's a Juneteenth sale that ends today
at amandalandexports.com.
And uh amandalandexports,
you can Well, first off, let me just
show you my album. So, this is my album
Truth Translator.
Yeah, you don't need a certificate. Just
jump in.
And
you can go to amandalandexports.com.
You can get
Oh, sorry. I thought I had stopped
sharing. Okay. At amandalandexports.com,
you can get books, you can get
notebooks,
you can get T-shirts.
I'll show you some of the stuff.
We've been walking this same old road.
Someone asked how was my event? Oh, you
can also, for $20, you can get my entire
music library, by the way. On Bandcamp,
for 20 bucks, you can get all of my
albums, including this one.
And shout out to Bandcamp. They're great
for independent creatives.
And
um of which I am one.
So,
what was I going Someone asked me how my
event was in Harlem.
My event in Harlem was so good that I
will now be doing a monthly there.
So, in New York City, you will be able
to come and join me monthly starting the
second Wednesday. That's right, Claire,
only $20.
Um
starting Wednesday starting July Sorry.
Starting July
8th,
you'll be able to join me on Wednesdays.
I mean, sorry. Let me get it together.
I'm trying to multitask. I'm not doing
well. Starting July 8th, you'll be able
to join me every second Wednesday
at Comedy in Harlem
for
Radical for Radical Rhythms experience.
Lloyd X knows is I have great politics.
That's the thing. It's not politics. I
just have committed principles.
I don't have politics.
You know, I think that it's it's it's
really bugged out how they have they
have effectively got folks to think of
their politics as something different
than their values. And the truth is
there there should be no politics. There
should be only values.
You know, that's why they do this thing
where they show you these presidents
with um you know, with having pets and
stuff and and oh, look at them with
their families. And it's like
Yeah, they're literally merking people
like every day.
What about those people's families?
How does that work?
And then they convince you that
basically
They convi- they convince you
that basically
um those families don't matter.
We're keeping your family safe.
>> I have really good upper body strength.
So, I don't know. Just don't believe the
height.
And
ultimately
Thank you, Marquis.
This lactician in Harlem
hit me and was like, "When are you going
to come to my spot?" And I was like,
"Oh, I figured out how to do my hair
myself."
And they said, "Well, when are you going
to promote my my shop?"
So, here's something I'm thinking about.
I would love to be mutual aid concept
for
my show in Harlem.
Because I'll offer it
on
um
I'll offer it on live for Patreon.
And the subscription to Patreon is only
$5.
And I would love to do something where
we collect
I don't know if this is even possible.
Where I just make a flat rate and folks
can just donate to that flat rate.
And so when folks come to the show,
they're just coming in cuz I've already
been compensated.
I'm not I'm not collaborating with
nobody.
>> Amanda Seales goes live and shares some
life updates as she was trying to unlock
um
lock her dreads like she said she
learned how to to make that
uh by herself and then she shares about
uh what's going on in her music career
and some of them match that
she has the sales so comment, like,
share, and also subscribe. Bye.